ollocard.com 2019-05-18

# Privacy Policy

Effective Date: January 2018.

This Online Privacy Policy ("Policy") applies to this Ollo Card Services (herein "we", "us", or "our") online interface (i.e., website or mobile application) and any Ollo Card Services interface that links to this Policy (each, a "Site", and, collectively, "Sites"). This Policy describes how Sites may collect, use, and share information from or about you. By using the Site, you agree to the terms and conditions of this Policy.

## COLLECTING AND USING PERSONAL INFORMATION

Personal Information means personally identifiable information such as information you provide to us online including name, postal or email addresses, telephone, fax or mobile numbers, or account numbers. We may also collect demographic information or other information provided by you such as your date of birth or household income. In some instances, we may collect personal information from you offline, or we may collect personal information about you from other sources, such as consumer reporting agencies. We may combine such other information with the personal information that we collect through the Site. We may collect and use Personal Information:

  * to respond to your inquiries and fulfill your requests;

  * to inform you about important information regarding the Site; products or services for which you apply or may be interested in applying for, or in which you are already enrolled; changes to terms, conditions, and policies; and/or other administrative information;

  * to personalize your experience on the Site;

  * to allow you to apply for products or services and evaluate your eligibility for such products or services;

  * to verify your identity and/or location (or the identity or location of your representative or agent) in order to allow access to your accounts, conduct online transactions, and to maintain measures aimed at preventing fraud and protecting the security of account and Personal Information;

  * for business purposes, including data analysis, audits, developing and improving products and services, enhancing the Site, identifying usage trends, and determining the effectiveness of promotional campaigns;

  * for risk control, for fraud detection and prevention, to comply with laws and regulations, and to comply with other legal process and law enforcement requirements; and

  * to allow you to utilize features within our Sites by granting us access to information from your device such as contact lists or geo-location when you request certain services.

### How Personal Information is Shared

Please see the Privacy Notice for information on how Personal Information about our customers may be shared and how you may be able to limit certain types of sharing.

We may share Personal Information as follows:

  * with service providers that help us perform Site functions and administer our services, such as third-party customer service providers;

  * in connection with a merger, acquisition, consolidation, change of control, or sale of all or a portion of our assets or if we undergo bankruptcy or liquidation;

  * with consumer reporting agencies;

  * in order to detect, investigate, prevent, or take action against illegal activities, fraud, or situations involving potential threats to the rights, property, or personal safety of any person;

  * where we are legally required to do so, such as in response to court orders or legal process; to establish, protect, or exercise our legal rights; to defend against legal claims or demands; or to comply with the requirements of any mandatory applicable law; or

  * with your consent.

### Information We Collect Automatically

We may automatically collect information that does not reveal your specific identity or does not directly relate to an individual, such as browser information, information collected through cookies, pixel tags and other technologies, and aggregated and de-identified data.

We collect and use such information:

  * Through your browser or device: Certain information is collected by most browsers and/or through your device, such as your Media Access Control (MAC) address, device type, screen resolution, operating system version, and internet browser type and version. We use this information to ensure Sites function properly, for fraud detection and prevention, and security purposes.

Your IP Address is a number that is automatically assigned to the device that you are using by your Internet Service Provider (ISP). An IP Address is identified and logged automatically in our server log files whenever a user visits the Site, along with the time of the visit and the page(s) that were visited. Collecting IP Addresses is standard practice on the internet and is done automatically by many websites. We use IP Addresses for purposes such as calculating Site usage levels, helping diagnose server problems, to personalize/tailor your experience while engaging with us online and offline, for compliance and security purposes, for advertising, and for administering the Site.

  * Using cookies: Cookies are pieces of information stored directly on the device you are using. Cookies allow us to collect information such as browser type, time spent on the Site, pages visited, language preferences, and your relationship with us. We use the information for security purposes, to facilitate navigation, to display information more effectively, to personalize/tailor your experience while engaging with us, and to recognize your device to allow your use of our online products and services. We collect statistical information about the usage of the Site in order to continually improve the design and functionality, to monitor responses to our advertisements and content, to understand how account holders and visitors use the Site, and to assist us with resolving questions regarding the Site.

You can refuse to accept these cookies, and most devices and browsers offer their own privacy settings for cookies. You will need to manage your cookie settings for each device and browser you use. However, if you do not accept these cookies, you may experience some inconvenience in your use of the Site and some online products and services. For example, we will not be able to recognize your device and you will need to answer a challenge question each time you log on. You also may not receive tailored advertising or other offers from us that may be relevant to your interests and needs.

  * Using other technologies including pixel tags, web beacons, and clear GIFs: These may be used in connection with some Site pages, downloadable mobile applications, and HTML-formatted email messages to measure the effectiveness of our communications, the success of our marketing campaigns, to compile statistics about usage and response rates, to personalize/tailor your experience while engaging with us online and offline, for fraud detection and prevention, for security purposes, for advertising, and to assist us in resolving account holders’ questions regarding use of our Site.

  * Using Flash objects: As part of our solutions for online authentication, we use Flash objects (sometimes referred to as "Local Shared Objects") to help us recognize you and your device when you come back to the Site. For our pages running Adobe® Flash® content (demos and tutorials with moving content), we use Flash objects to determine your browser type and version of Adobe Flash in order for you to view the content. We do not use Flash objects for any online behavioral advertising purpose. Deleting cookies does not delete Flash objects. You can learn more about Flash objects - including how to control and disable them - through the Adobe interface. If you choose to disable Flash objects from our Site, then you may not be able to access and use all or part of the Site or benefit from the information and services offered.

Some content or applications on the Site may be provided by third parties, including analytics companies and advertising providers. These third parties may use cookies or other tracking technologies to collect information about you when you use our Site. The information they collect may be associated with your Personal Information or they may collect information, including Personal Information, about your online activities over time and across different websites and other online services.

One of the third-party services that we use is Google Analytics, which is a web analysis service provided by Google. Google utilizes the data collected to track and examine the use of our Site and may share this data with other Google services. You can learn more about how Google uses and shares Personal Information and about any choices you may have with regards to your Personal Information by visiting their website at [www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/](https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/).

## Linking to other websites

We may provide links to third party websites, such as credit bureaus, service providers, or merchants. If you follow links to websites not affiliated or controlled by Ollo Card Services, you should review their privacy and security policies and other terms and conditions, as they may be different from those of our Sites. We do not guarantee and are not responsible for the privacy or security of these websites, including the accuracy, completeness, or reliability of their information.

## Security

To protect Personal Information from unauthorized access and use, we use security measures that comply with applicable federal and state laws. These measures may include device safeguards and secured files and buildings as well as oversight of our third-party service providers to ensure information remains confidential and secure.

## Making changes to your Personal Information

Keeping your account information accurate and up to date is very important. If your account information is incomplete, inaccurate, or not current, please call us at 1-877-494-0020 or write to us at Ollo Card Services, PO Box 9222, Old Bethpage, NY 11804.

## Protecting children’s privacy online

The Site is not directed to individuals under the age of thirteen (13) years, and we request that children under the age of 13 years do not provide Personal Information through the Site. We do not knowingly collect information from children under 13 years without parental consent. Visit the Federal Trade Commission website for more information about the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act ("COPPA").

## Updates to this Privacy Notice

This Online Privacy Policy is subject to change. Please review it periodically. If we make changes to this Policy, any changes to this Policy will become effective when we post the revised Policy on the Site. Your use of the Site following these changes means that you accept the revised Policy.
